(Sheldon:)Captain Kirk won.
(Penny:)Kirk cheated.
(Sheldon:)Impressive that you know that.
(Sheldon:)It's hard to believe
(Sheldon:)I'm actually having
this conversation with you.
(Penny:)Right there with you.
(Sheldon:)Kirk beat the Kobayashi Maru
by reprogramming the simulator.
(Sheldon:)That's it.
What?
(Sheldon:)I'll reprogram Howard.
What...?
(Penny:)Sheldon, you can't
reprogram people.
No, you can't reprogram people.
(Sheldon:)To James Tiberius Kirk.
(Sheldon:)Hello, all.
(Leonard:)- Hello.
- Hey.
(Sheldon:)Howard, you're feeling better
about me today, aren't you?
(Howard:)Not really.
(Sheldon:)Yes, you are.
(Sheldon:)I'm using
neurolinguistic programming
(Sheldon:)to modify your thought patterns.